Born 1993, Baku Azerbaijan

Address Warsaw, Poland 00 - 732

Contact

+48 662 124 745 nijatsafarli@gmail.com

Portfolio on my website nijatsafarli.com







<u>Graphic Designer</u>

With over 7 years of experience as a graphic designer and design manager, I've been on a journey to find the best design solutions for a variety of industries including oil, construction, electronics, banking, software and more. I firmly believe that good design is a critical element for businesses to develop and expand. It's a great joy for me to utilize my skills and experience to impact this process.

It all started with pencil drawings. First, it was just a hobby, but it eventually became a professional pleasure. As an illustrator, I incorporate my drawing skills into nearly every project, creating a unique style for each design solution. Besides using illustrations in most projects, I also developed myself as an individual artist and started creating numerous illustrations for pure enjoyment. Even though it's still a professional hobby, it's also a desired skill for many

WORK EXPERIENCE

PLANHAT LLC

[Customer Success Software Platform]

Sweden / Full-time remote work

Digital Designer

- Creating all design creatives of company
- Creating visual concepts of documents, e-books and catalogues
- Re-shaping design structure of company
- Creating web illustrations for website and application
- Designing webinar and podcast visuals

AZERBAIJAN NATIONAL ANTI-DOPING AGENCY (AMADA)

[Govermental sport inspection organisation]

June 2020 - December 2021

Design Manager

- Manage and create all design creatives of company
- Creating visual concepts of events and conferences • Leading photographes&videographes shooting and
- finalizing products with them • Creating educational anti-doping materials, such as, flyers,
- presentations, handbooks, social media posters and etc. Participating in departmental strategic planning
- Creating annual report catalogue by unique concepts

ATL CONSULTING LLC

[360° marketing service- Advertisement company]

May 2019 - June 2020

Graphic Designer

- Presenting the briefs and concepts based on the client's needs and vision
- Working with copywriter and creative director to produce final design
- Creating visual concepts in line with the customer's needs · Providing graphic images, illustrations, motion videos,
- retouched images, web designs, print materials, mockups and sketches Participating in departmental strategic planning

BAKU ELECTRONICS LLC

[Chain of the biggest electronics household product stores

May 2018 - March 2019

Graphic Designer

- Creating social media image and video visuals
- Designing print materials, e-books, catalogues, billboards, promo materials, flyer and posters based on campaigns or creative directions · Creating key visuals for sale campaigns and adapting
 - it to various layouts and also to HTML5 banners

TECHNOL LLC [First motor oil company in Caucasus]

May 2017 - May 2018

Graphic Designer

- Conceptualizing visuals based on creative directions
- Thinking creatively to produce new ideas and concepts and developing interactive design Creating daily social media images, GIFs and videos
- Design product labels and preparing them ready for print

FREELANCE WORK EXPERIENCE Feburary 2016 - Present

Freelance works have always been an opportunity to enter a different business fields. Besides permanent job freelancing is a great way of enlarging portfolio with different kind of projecst and companies.



Technol



WKargoFly



Eexpressbank







BSc Business Administration Akdeniz University

EDUCATION

Business Administration & Management

Erasmus Exchange Programme January 2014 - July 2014

2011-2015

Tartu University Estonia, Tartu

Turkey, Antalya

DESIGN SKILLS

Azerbaijan / Native

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Adobe InDesign **Adobe After Effects** Corel Draw Suit Adobe XD Figma Blender Google Web Designer **Audacity**

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

SOFTWARE KNOWLEDGE

Graphic Design Pencil drawing **Art Direction** Background Design Illustration Branding

Character Design 3D knowledge **Motion Graphics** Web Design Video Editing

Turkish / Native English / Advanced Russian / Elementary Polish/ Elementary

Fully/Part-time working

OTHER SKILLS

Communication skills

Creative thinking

Full Management ability

Innovative approach

Analytic solving



Availibility to travel

Extensive experience with computer software&hardware

SOCIAL MEDIA PROFILES

/ Digital Pen



/nijatsafarli

Nijat Safarli

www.nijatsafarli.com Last updated in August 2023